{
    "subject": "resource/A_Shoreline_Dream",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "A Shoreline Dream's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9448248147964478,
            "question": "Is A Shoreline Dream based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983303308486938,
            "question": "What country is A Shoreline Dream's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8269197344779968,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about A Shoreline Dream's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076510429382324,
            "question": "If you were to visit A Shoreline Dream's hometown, where would you go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7989946603775024,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in A Shoreline Dream's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7963488101959229,
            "question": "Where is A Shoreline Dream from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7899446487426758,
            "question": "Is A Shoreline Dream a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7783210873603821,
            "question": "What is the culture like in A Shoreline Dream's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7015998363494873,
            "question": "Where was A Shoreline Dream originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5861571431159973,
            "question": "What is the nationality of A Shoreline Dream?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Shoreline Dream's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9302_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was A Shoreline Dream originally from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9302_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the culture like in A Shoreline Dream's hometown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9302_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is A Shoreline Dream a band from the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9302_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9302_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n* A Shoreline Dream is from Denver, Colorado, in the United States.\n* A Shoreline Dream is an indie rock band.\n* This year (2022), they've decided to do something a little different by releasing a trilogy of EPs.\n\nThe answer is: \n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about A Shoreline Dream, indicating they are an indie rock band from Denver, Colorado, United States. This supports the statement that A Shoreline Dream's hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}